Foreign Film mss., 1939-1962 LMC 1379
Lilly Library
Foreign Films mss.
1939-1962
Lilly Library
LMC 1379
1 Box 1 standard
The Foreign film mss., 1939-1962, consists of movie stills from 23 foreign films.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Scope and Content Note
Some of the films represented include: The Ladykillers (Great Britain, 1955), The Music Room (India, 1958), The Red Balloon (France, 1955), and The Seventh Seal (Sweden, 1957). They are filed in chronological order by release date.
Acquisition Information
Transfer: 1996
Motion picture film; Foreign films
- Volpone, 1939 (Box 1)
- Torment, 1944 (Box 1)
- Children of Paradise, 1945 (Box 1)
- Manon, 1949 (Box 1)
- Three Strange Loves, 1949 (Box 1)
- To Paris with Love, 1954 (Box 1)
- The Seven Samurai, 1954 (Box 1)
- The Ladykillers, 1955 (Box 1)
- The Red Balloon, 1955 (Box 1)
- The Seventh Seal, 1957 (Box 1)
- Carry On Admiral, 1957 (Box 1)
- The Awakening, 1958 (Box 1)
- The Hidden Fortress, 1958 (Box 1)
- The Music Room, 1958 (Box 1)
- The Firebird, 1959 (Box 1)
- Odd Obsession, 1959 (Box 1)
- The Possessors, 1960 (Box 1)
- Don Quixote, 1961 (Box 1)
- La Notte Brava, 1960 (Box 1)
- The Trial, 1962 (Box 1)
- Therese Desqueyroux, 1962 (Box 1)
- Neopolitan Carousel undated (Box 1)
- Unknown, undated (Box 1)